seta

gauravsetaportfolio .herokuapp.com <u>LINKEDIN</u>: gauravGAURAV SETA +91-8097699073 gauravseta@gmail.com

Gaurav is a **Frontend developer** with **4 years of experience** who loves exploring different web technologies and learning about them. Goal is to succeed in an environment of growth and excellence.

EMPLOYERS:

TCS (Tata Consultancy Services) - (Sep 2015 - Feb 2018)

Miles India - (Feb 2018 - July 2018)

Varian Medical Systems - (July 2018 - Present)

SKILLS

Domains: Frontend (web), Unit-testing, DevOps

Languages: Javascript, Java

Frameworks: React, Angular, AngularJS State Management Libraries: Redux, NGXS

Preprocessors: SASS, LESS

Server Side: Node.js

Tools: Heroku, S3, CircleCl, Docker **Version Control:** Github, Gitlab

EXPERIENCE

VAIS (Varian Authentication & Identity Services), Front End Developer, 2018-Present

- Developed various new pure components using ReactJS.
- Co-ordinated with design team for UX feasibility.

VAMP (Varian Authentication & Management Portal), Front End Developer, 2018-Present

- Developed complete website from scratch using **Angular 7**.
- Co-ordinated with design team for UX feasibility.

Inixy Easy Control, Front End Developer, Summer 2018

- Edited an existing bootstrap theme according to the client's needs.
- Created Grunt tasks to output the minified code.
- Created various responsive components and page templates for the website.

Axis Bank, Front End Developer, 2016-2018

- Developed various new components in existing official banking website.
- Created website components using HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, AngularJS.

Mitsubishi Connect, Front End Developer, 2015-2016

- Developed a complete website with all its pages from design files.
- Created responsive cross browser web pages from given PSD files.

EDUCATION

Shri Guru Gobind Singhji Institute of Engineering & Technology, 2011-15 Bachelor of Technology, Electronics & Communication, 7.4/10

PROJECTS

Portfolio, 2018

• <u>Created</u> a simple UI page using **HTML5**, **AngularJS**, **CSS3** (**Flex box layout**) for demo purpose.